Hey , get away from me with that pail of water . I 'll kill you .
Hey , what was the elbow for , asshole ?
Yeah , nice pitch ! Get two , get two , get two !
Cut it out ! Daddy , tell him to leave me alone .
- Peter started it ! - I did not , you liar !
- Did too . - Did not .
Alright , let 's settle down and stop fighting .
She started it .
That looks neat . Can I try it , Daddy ?
Maybe in a couple years , if we ever get a motorboat .
Can we go to the camp one summer ? I bet they 'd show us there .
Well , I don 't know about that .
Hang in there , Dolore ! You 're doing great !
Can 't we stop now ?
Hey , Craig . How about letting me take her out once , huh ?
Come on , Mary Ann . You know I can 't do that .
Oh , don 't be such a stiff . I know how to drive these things .
My old man 's got one twice as big .
Yeah , and is your old man gonna give me a job when I get fired ?
Lighten up , will you ? No one 's gonna see us way out here .
Oh , so you think it 's funny , huh ? You little schemers !
Come on . Please ?
Alright .
Super !
But look , just for a minute .
Not too fast !
Hey John , we gotta go meet the Doc .
John ! It 's almost 4 : 30 . Doc 's gonna be here soon !
Come on , fellas . Doctor Thomas is on her way up .
- Aunt Martha 's coming ? - Is Ricky coming too ?
Nah , I 'm afraid he 's spending the weekend with his father .
You look like a skiing hunchback ! Straighten up , will ya ?
Turn ! Turn the boat !
- What 'd she say ? - I don 't know .
Hey !
There 's a boat !
Stop the motor . Holy shit ! Turn it !
Turn the wheel !
- I can 't turn it ! - Give me the wheel !
John !
Oh my God !
Somebody help those people ! Get in the water !
Get them onto the boat , please ! Oh my God , we just hit them both .
Oh my God .
Somebody help them . Please .
Help them ! Please ! They 're gonna die , I know it ! Please !
Hurry ! Help them ! Please help them !
Oh my God , we just hit them both .
Hurry , sweeties . We don 't want to be late for the bus .
Goodness , no . That wouldn 't do at all .
Richard . Angela . Oh , here you are .
Look what I did . I packed you and your cousin some goodies
for the ride up to camp . Wasn 't that nice of me , hmm ?
Any Chips ?
Why , of course . I believe there 's a whole bag .
I 'm almost sure of it .
Angela , isn 't there anything special my little girl would care for , hmm ?
We gotta go , mom . It 's getting late .
Well of course you do , dear . We wouldn 't want them to leave without us ,
now would we ?
No . No , I 'm afraid that that wouldn 't do .
Come , children . Let 's be on our way .
Now what ?
I believe that I 've forgotten something . Now , what can it be ?
Oh , I remember what it is . I knew I would forget .
I just kept reminding myself . In fact , I tied a string around ...
Around my finger , so I wouldn 't forget .
See ?
And I didn 't . You never can be too careful .
Well , what is it already ?
Oh , just a moment ! I 'll be right back !
Good old Mom 's at it again .
Here they are ! All filled out and signed by yours truly .
Wasn 't that nice of me , hmm ?
- What are they ? - Why , they 're your physicals , of course .
We can 't go to camp without our physicals , now can we ?
Just be careful not to tell anyone how you got them .
Oh , no , I 'm afraid that they wouldn 't approve of that at all .
Even though they know that I am a doctor .
No matter what they do , I 'll never tell .
Oh , you 're such a dear .
Well , run along now .
- So long , Mom . - Goodbye , my angel .
I hope you have a good time . But of course you will .
Take good care of my little girl , Richard !
- Goodbye , Mom . - Goodbye , dear .
Look at all that young , fresh chicken . Where I come from we call them baldies .
Makes your mouth water , don 't it ?
Artie . They 're too young to even understand what 's on your mind .
Ben , good buddy , there ain 't any such thing as being too young .
You 're just too old .
Ahh ! Ricky , how you doin ' ?
- Paul , great to see you . - You winning ?
Ah , you know . Same old shit .
- Hey , this is my cousin Angela . - How you doin ' ?
She 's kind of shy , I guess . You know , first time away from home and all .
Listen , I got to take her down to the bunks .
I 'll catch you down the hill , ok ?
You got it .
Hey , Rick .
Wait 'll you get a load of Judy !
Man , oh , man .
Oh , yeah ?
You 'll see .
Me and Judy were steadies last summer .
Hey , you 'll probably be in the same cabin .
These are all the girls ' cabins .
Over there is the rec hall . Next to that is Ronnie 's shack .
Behind that 's the archery range . There she is !
Judy ! Yo , Judy ! How you doin ' ?
Alright .
Who 's the wimp ?
Oh , that 's Ricky .
Wasn 't he the kid you were babysitting last year ?
Guess I 'm not good enough for her anymore .
Well , here you go , Angela .
If you need anything , I 'll be in bunk 19 , below .
Second from the bottom .
- Who were those guys ? - Just some boys I met today .
Weren 't they a little old for you ?
Don 't you know girls mature before boys ?
That 's bullshit and you know it .
Ricky , I don 't have time for your nonsense right now .
Well , excuse me . Bitch .
Alright , ladies . Let 's hurry it up and unpack
so we can get these trunks the hell out of here .
By the way , for those of you who don 't know , the name is Meg .
M-E-G .
This here is Susie . You got any problems , this is the complaint department .
Got it ? Ok ? Capische ?
What are you looking at ?
What , are you taking pictures ? Quit it !
You must be Angela . Remember ? Ronnie spoke to us about her .
Looks like we got a real winner here .
You ain 't kidding .
Quiet , please .
Thanks for nothing .
See what I mean , Ronnie ? She hasn 't even touched it .
Angela , Meg tells me you haven 't eaten much since you 've been here .
Is that true ?
You won 't get a peep out of this one . She hasn 't said a word in three days .
Tell you what . How about if you and me take a walk into the kitchen ?
See if we can find something you like . That sound okay ?
I 'm gonna take her inside to see Artie . She 'll be alright .
Probably a little homesick , is all .
Come on , Angela .
He 's starting to spoil the little brat already .
Hey Ben , is Artie around ? Artie , can I see you for a minute , please ?
Hey , Artie . Be a little more discrete with the beer can , huh ?
Sure , Ron . What 's up ?
I want you to meet one of our new campers . Angela , this is Artie , our head chef .
Well , hello there , Angela .
Can you get that , Ben ? Please ?
As you can see , she isn 't very talkative .
In fact , she isn 't much of a fan of your cooking , either .
You think you could find something for her ? Some ice cream , or , you know ...
Phone for you and Mel , Ron .
Do me a favor . Get Mel , will you ?
See what you can do , okay , Artie ? I 'll catch you later .
No problem . I 'll find something she likes .
I 'll bet we can find something interesting in the walk-in .
You never know what you can find in there .
Where 's my cousin ?
Ronnie took her into the kitchen .
- She eat anything ? - What do you think ?
What 's her problem , anyway ? She don 't eat , she don 't talk , she don 't do anything .
Why don 't you leave her alone ? She 's just quiet .
If she were any quieter , she 'd be dead .
So Angela , see anything you like ?
Maybe I can help you decide .
You sure are a sweet-looking little cupcake , ain 't you ?
Yeah . Think I got something you 're gonna like real good .
Hey , what are you doing ? !
Keep your mouth shut , you hear me ?
You didn 't see nothin ' ! Got it ? Nothin ' !
- Sure . Whatever you want . - Now get the hell out of here .
Hey , What 's going on ?
What was that all about ?
Guess I scared him .
I guess so .
Want to check on the water ? About done over here .
That damn water better be done . It 's been on a half hour . Shit !
- Gimme that goddamn chair . - All yours , my good man .
It 's still got a couple minutes to go .
Gonna grab some hay before dinner . You coming ?
- Yeah , after I throw the corn in . - See you later .
Boiling yet ?
Atta girl .
Motherfucker , you could have killed me !
Now get the hell over here and help me down .
Come on , kid .
Get me down and I 'll make you a nice ice cream sundae , okay ?
Hey , what the ... What the hell you doin ' ? !
You little shit !
When I get down from here I 'm gonna rip your fucking head off !
Ben ! Help ! Ben !
Ben ! Get the hell in here ! Ben !
Help ! Ben ! Ben !
Ben !
I 'm afraid I don 't carry a sedative strong enough to mask
the kind of agony he 's in right now . Every
nerve in his body must feel like it 's on fire .
What 's the prognosis , Doc ?
Well , he 's badly burned all over .
Especially his face .
How about his eyes ?
Too early to tell .
Jesus , the pain must be incredible .
Poor guy must be going crazy .
Yeah , if he 's lucky .
Look , can we move this along , please ?
No need to upset the campers , right ?
Well , I guess I 'll be on my way .
Now what ?
Now we get this ambulance out of here as quickly as we can .
Why ? It was only an accident .
Because I don 't want the kids
or their parents to know that this ever happened .
You understand ?
What about them ?
Don 't worry .
I 'll take care of them .
Real shame what happened to Artie in here .
In the future , I hope the rest of you will be more careful .
Ben ?
I guess that makes you the head man here now , doesn 't it ?
I wasn 't thinking much about myself , Mr. Costa .
I just don 't see how something like that could happen .
Come on now , Ben . We still got a camp to feed here now , don 't we ?
Yes , sir .
Besides , fifty bucks more a week can 't be all that bad , now , can it ?
No , sir . I always thought he had a little devil in him .
And fifteen dollars a week more for the rest of you , eh ?
- That 's real generous of you , sir . - Well , now ...
Ben , there is one thing , though ...
There 's really no reason for the campers to find out what happened .
You know what I mean ?
Too , um ,
gruesome , I think .
So why don 't we just say that Artie
found himself another job , should anybody happen to ask .
Sure , sure . Whatever you say , sir .
Good , and do me a favor . Tell your friends here to say the same thing .
You don 't have to worry none about them .
Good . Thanks , Ben . I knew I could count on you .
What do you say we get dinner going here , huh ?
Right away , sir .
Mind over matter is the key .
Mind over matter says that even the incredibly simple task
of a single sit-up
should be impossible ,
should the mind will it .
Come on . There 's no way .
Shut up , Mozart , and concentrate .
Concentrate on summoning all your strength for this single sit-up .
And you will be amazed when the time comes
that although the body is willing ,
the mind refuses .
I will count to three .
On three , you will concentrate all your strength ,
only to see the folly of it all .
Concentrate , dear boy . I cannot stress this enough .
Mind over matter . Mind over matter .
I shall now begin the count .
One .
Two .
Three !
You guys are gross !
Don 't tell me Mozart fell for the old mind over matter trick .
Oh , not Mozart . He 's too swift for that .
Hey , listen . Everybody grab your glove . The games are on .
- They 're gonna play us ? - Right now .
I got five bucks riding on you guys , so don 't lose .
No sweat , Gene . We 're gonna kick their asses .
Alright , you better . Let 's go .
Come on , Ricky , babe . Save me my ups .
Hey ! Big man !
You and your boys want to place a little wager while the game is still close ?
What do you have in mind , asswipe ?
- Buck a man , asshole ! - That 's a little steep .
- Make it five . - You got it .
Come on , Chuck , he 's a looker .
Nice shot , Rick , way to go !
Go Paul ! Come on , Paul .
Make yourself useful and bring me home , huh ?
This little shit , will be lucky to make contact .
Should 've brought my rabbit 's foot .
You got it , you got it , you got it !
You got it ! Come on ! Get it ! Get it !
Safe !
- Nice shot , man . - Must have been lucky .
Come on , Billy , be a hitter Bill . Come on , Bill !
No problem Geno , this guy blows dead dogs . Just lay it in there .
- Eat shit and die , Ricky ! - Eat shit and live , Bill .
Yea Bill , he 's a little wimp , Bill .
Come on , keep your eye on it . Drive it in . Let 's go .
Right there , Bill ! Go ahead . Go ! Go ! Go !
Wake up Mo !
Shit .
Come on , Mo !
You got it , babe !
Nice catch , Motz .
Get off , man .
Can you believe that ? Hey , how many we up by now , anyway ?
I think it 's 8-6 .
Come on . Take the bat off your shoulder .
Fuck you !
You tell him too , Rick . You tell him , too .
What are you gonna do with your big paycheck ?
I don 't know ! Maybe I 'll get a Corvette or something .
How about you ?
I think I 'll take a cruise .
Hey , Mr. G ! How about some real competition next time ?
Yeah ! Maybe the girls want a game !
It 's okay , we 'll get ' em back . Come on , we 'll get ' em back .
Don 't worry . We 'll get ' em back .
We still need more babes .
I mean , who wants to go skinny dipping with fifteen guys and only five girls ?
Hey , let 's ask Angela .
Man , I 've been watching her a whole week , and she is fucked up .
Now wait a second . You guys aren 't afraid to ask Angela , are you ?
I think it might be kind of interesting if Angela were around tonight .
Good . Then you ask her .
Oh , I would , but it wasn 't my idea .
Hey , and who am I to steal a buddy 's great idea , huh ?
Unless , of course , you guys are ... chicken !
Alright ! Alright , we 'll do it !
Who knows ? We may get married one day .
Nice shot .
Say , Angela . We 're all going down to the lake tonight .
You know , for a little swim . And , um , we were kind of wondering if , well ,
maybe if you wanted to join us or something .
Let the pro take over .
Listen Angela , what say me and you go for a little walk somewhere , talk about tonight , huh ?
What 's the matter , can 't you talk ?
I told you she was playing with half a deck . Angela 's a nut cake .
Ain 't that right , Angela ? Ain 't you Looney Tunes ?
Hey Angela , how 's this ? Remind you of anyone you know ?
Yo , Angela . How come you 're so fucked up ?
I mean , like , what 's your problem ?
Hey , dickface , leave her alone .
Oh yeah ? What are you gonna do about it , asshole ?
You fucks ! I 'm gonna beat your fucking asses in !
You and what army ?
Oh , shut up and let 's go .
Come on .
Pricks !
Shut your mouth , will you , Mel 's here ?
I don 't give a shit .
I think I 'd better take you over to the infirmary before your mouth gets you
into any more trouble .
- You alright ? - Yeah , I guess so .
Don 't worry about it , Rick . We 'll get ' em back .
Come on , let 's get out of here .
Hi . I 'm Paul . Remember ?
I met you last week when we all first got here .
Listen , I heard ... Well , I mean , Ricky told me all about it .
Well anyway , I 'm really sorry about what happened to your family .
Me and Ricky , we go back a long time .
We 've been best friends for three years already .
We always seem to get into trouble together .
Last year we hung the girls ' panties on the flagpole .
Sorry .
We got caught anyway .
Could be a lot of rocks .
Jerk .
Then there was this time last year ...
We locked Alan Weinstein out of the cabin with no clothes on .
Boy , did we get it for that one .
Hey , bunk 19 , time to go . Say your goodnights and move out .
Guess I gotta go . Well , goodnight , Angela .
Goodnight .
Good night !
Come on , girls !
Water 's really warm at night . What do you say , huh ?
- I don 't know , Billy . - It 's all very simple , right ?
Why don 't you start without us ?
The hell with you , then !
You don 't know how to have any fun anyways .
Come on , boys .
- Come on , be serious . - I am serious .
Woo !
Whoa !
Oh !
Any of you ladies interested in a moonlight canoe ride ?
Hey , come on . I won 't try anything , I promise .
How about it , Betsy ?
No , I don 't think so , Kenny .
Leslie 's coming down soon . Why don 't you ask her ?
Leslie 's coming down ?
Definitely , definitely .
Take it easy .
Have a good trip .
I don 't like the way he said that . Are you two planning something ?
Relax , Leslie . You can trust me . Mike 's always screwing around like that .
The water really does feel warmer at night .
Better not leave your hand in there too long .
All the water snakes and snapping turtles come out at night .
Yeah , sure .
Really ! If you fall in , you 're gonna get eaten alive .
Hey , quit rockin ' it , will you ?
Why ? You 're not scared of a few snakes and turtles , are you ?
Kenny , stop it ! I want to go back .
You know , if we fall in , we may never be seen again !
You bastard ! I hate you .
Hey , that 's not a water snake I see over there , is it ?
Leslie ...
Les-lie ...
Hey !
Hey , you !
You guys are real schmucks .
Hey , Leslie ! See any water snakes out there ?
Woooo !
Hey , Bob-a-Ray-Bob . Hey , hey , Bob-a-Ray-Bob .
What the hell are you doing here ?
I bet the rest of the boys 'll be interested in seeing you .
Hey , Kenny ! You scared all the chicks away !
That 's Kenny .
Love him and leave him .
Hey , we better beat it before all those girls get caught and tell Ronnie we 're
all down here .
Is this what 's called getting caught with your pants down ?
Aw , you stupid shit .
Woo !
Kenny , let 's go !
Come on , we 're out of here !
Fuck him , Mike ! He 's being a wise-ass again !
We 'll catch him back at the bunk .
Why do I have to clean up after these little peckerheads ?
It 's not my camp .
You 'd think I didn 't have anything better to do !
These peckerheads suck !
How the hell did that get there ?
Pick up this . Pick up that . Clean this . Clean that .
Sign here , Mel .
I 'd like to see Mel get his fat ass down here and pick up something .
That cheap son of a ...
As far as I can tell , the boy drowned .
Of course , we 'll have to wait for the medical examiner to check him over
before we can be certain .
Of course he drowned . He was horsing around , the canoe tipped over .
He must have hit his head .
I don 't think so . Weren 't any bumps or bruises when I checked .
Though again , I 'm no expert on this matter .
It was obviously an accident . I mean , the boy might have gotten scared and panicked .
Right ?
That could be a logical explanation .
So it was one of those fluke accidents we could not have foreseen ,
and that is all there is to it !
- I don 't know Mel , I ... - It was an accident !
I mean , that 's what the officer said , right ?
I said the autopsy will be more conclusive .
Right .
- You 'll call me as soon as you know ? - You can count on it .
If you 'll excuse me I have the unpleasant task of
informing the boy 's parents .
Thank you for your help , officer .
The man doesn 't take no for an answer , does he ?
I guess he 's just uptight about bad publicity .
Yeah , I guess so .
Hey , weren 't you about to say something just before he bit your head off ?
I dunno . I was just thinking , I remember that boy being a pretty damn good swimmer .
I sure hope you 're wrong .
Alright , let 's go . Everyone back to their bunks .
Be ready for the morning activity . Come on , let 's go .
Nine , six .
Get it . Yeah !
Ten , six .
Hi-ya , Angela .
- How 's it going ? - Okay . How 's it going with you ?
Could be better . Your cousin just whipped me in tennis .
I was wondering ...
Want to go to the movie in the rec hall tonight ?
I thought we had to go anyway .
Yeah , we do . But I meant seeing it together .
So how about it ? You want to go ?
- Alright . - Great !
Hey . How come Angela gets to talk to the boys all day ?
And we have to play volleyball .
What 's she ? Special ?
It doesn 't seem fair , does it ?
- Aren 't you supposed to be somewhere ? - I 'm going .
- See you later , Angela . - Bye .
Listen , Angela .
If you 're not gonna participate in our activities ,
then you just sit there and do nothing .
That does not include talking with the boys .
You 're not a goddamn prima donna , you know ?
Understand ?
Big deal , she was talking to a boy . Let 's just finish the game
so we can get ready for lunch .
Yeah , let 's .
- Are you sure you don 't want to play ? - I 'm sure .
Is there anything you would like to do ? Go sailing or something ?
That 's okay . I don 't mind watching .
Twelve , seven .
Mind if I walk you back to your bunk ?
I guess not .
Gimme a break , will you ? Stop acting so stuck-up .
Remember all those good times we had last summer ?
What do you say , huh ? Let me walk you back ?
Not tonight , Ricky .
- Where are we going ? - I want to show you something .
I hope you 're not mad I did that .
I 'm not mad . I better go in .
Can I have another one ?
You know , another good night kiss ?
I have to go now .
Good night , Angela .
Good night .
Hello , Paul .
How you doing , Judy ?
You and Angela sure are becoming quite an item .
So what ?
I just didn 't think she was your type .
You know what I mean ?
I gotta go .
Boy , did I have a great time tonight .
Shh ! Shut up , or you 'll wake up Mozart .
What are you guys doing ?
You 'll see .
Go ahead , Baron . But don 't wake him up .
What the ... ?
What 's the matter , Motz ? Five-o-clock shadow ?
You bastard !
Look out , man , he 's got a knife !
I 'm gonna kill you !
Uh-oh !
Hey !
What , are you guys kidding me ?
Are you nuts or something ?
Gimme that . You 'll see this at the end of the summer , if you 're lucky .
Idiot .
Come on , Gino , he was just kidding .
Give him a break .
Yeah . Gimme a break .
Maybe I should ask Ronnie what he thinks I should do .
You 'll see it at the end of the summer . Right , now everybody into bed .
That includes you too , lover boy .
Guess who ?
- Um , Ricky . - Nope !
- Um ... Burt Reynolds ! - You 're getting warmer .
- I give up ! - Surprise !
Who are you ?
Well , well , if it isn 't the two lovebirds .
Why don 't you get out of here ?
Oh , sorry .
She 's such a jerk sometimes , isn 't she ?
Uh-oh . Here comes the wicked witch of the West .
I think I 'm gonna go back into the water .
Talk to you later , Angela .
Well , not going in the water again , huh , Angela ?
What 's the matter ? Don 't you like to swim ?
Can you swim ?
Angela , I 'm talking to you . Are you going in the water or aren 't you ?
Huh ? !
Angela ! I am waiting for an answer !
Yes or no ?
Goddammit , answer me , Angela ! Answer me ! Goddammit , answer me !
- What the hell is going on here ? - The little bitch won 't answer me !
She never answers me !
You alright , Angela ?
Meg , I want to see you in my shack right after swim period .
Now get back to your post .
Hey , girls .
Let 's not forget to thank Angela for getting Meg in trouble .
I didn 't do anything .
You never do shit .
Give me that .
Hey , Angela .
How come you never take showers when the rest of us do , huh ?
You queer or something ?
Oh , I know what it is . You haven 't reached puberty yet .
Is that it ?
I bet you don 't even have your period .
That 's enough , Judy !
Angela 's allowed to shower in the morning or any other time she wants to .
Yeah , she takes showers when no one can see she has no hair down below .
- Judy ! - She 's a real carpenter 's dream !
Flat as a board and needs a screw !
- That 's enough ! - Fuck off !
I 'm going down to see my cousin . I 'll be back before dinner .
You fucking bastards are gonna pay for this !
Cocksuckers ! Pricks !
I 'm gonna fight you , chickenshits !
- Angela ! - You chickenshits , you fucking pussies !
I 'll kick your friggin asses all over this goddamn camp , you fucks !
Those pricks , I 'll kill ' em !
Take it easy already !
You boys come down from there immediately .
Those cocksuckers keep picking on my cousin .
- That 's bullshit . - Enough .
I saw the whole business .
You realize how dangerous those things are ?
You could have taken her eye out .
Ronnie 's gonna hear about this ,
and there gonna be no canteen for a whole week .
And that goes for you too on account of your filthy mouth .
What ? !
If I ever hear anything like this again ,
I 'm gonna throw the whole bunch of you out of here ,
and don 't think I don 't mean it .
Get ready for dinner .
How do you feel , Angela ? Alright ?
She 's okay .
Better go change before you catch pneumonia . It 's almost time to eat .
Hey ! What are you guys up to , huh ?
We got a game against the counselors . You gonna play ?
Sure .
I gotta take a wicked dump first , so I 'll see you guys down there , alright ?
Got it . See you later .
Who is that ?
Oh , playing games ? Is that you , Benji ? Jesus Christ .
I can 't even take a shit in peace around here .
What the hell are you doing ? Hey , get that thing out of here !
Come on , get it out !
Come on ! Get it out ! Get it out ! No ! No ! No !
Oh , God ! Get away from me !
Get away ! Get away from me !
Get away , get away ! Somebody help ! Somebody help me !
Help me !
Help me , somebody !
I 'm finished !
That 's all there is to it . Finished . Wiped out .
How many are left ?
I 'd say about twenty-five .
We might as well pack everything and shut down .
Nobody 's ever gonna send their kids here again .
Why don 't we finish the summer , Mel ? Tomorrow I 'll consolidate the bunks .
There 's no sense in keeping everyone spread out .
Yeah .
Why make things easier for the killer ?
Hey , don 't talk like that . We don 't know anything for sure yet .
I know ! I 've known all along . I 've seen the hate in his eyes .
But I never did anything . Now , I 'll stop him for what he 's done to me .
I 'll stop him !
Snap out of it , will you , Mel ? You 're talking crazy .
Yeah , maybe I am . Maybe I 'm just ... imagining it .
Maybe .
Boo ! Scared you , huh ?
I thought you were the killer .
Oh , come on . Don 't tell me you believe all that bologna .
Yeah , well what happened to Billy ?
Somebody was playing a joke and it got out of hand .
Now come on . Let 's get out of here before we get caught .
- Or murdered . - Where are we going ?
To the lake .
Wait 'll I get my hands on you !
No , don 't .
Come on , Angela . I 'm not doing anything .
No !
Angela !
Okay , let me have your attention for one minute .
The last few days we 've been using the regular activity schedule .
And that bites the big one ,
so today we 're going to try something a little different , okay ?
Like in Color War , you 're gonna be separated into
two groups and we 're gonna play capture the flag .
For you guys who have never played before , Gene is going to explain the rules .
Alright , gangsters , listen up , because this is going to be a lot of fun .
Now , depending on what team you 're on , you 're going to be wearing white strips
or blue strips . The guys with the blue strips have to capture the white flag ,
and the guys with the white strips have to capture the blue flag .
Sounds easy enough , right ?
Now , to capture the flag you 've got to sneak into the other guy 's territory .
Capture his flag without getting one of your strips taken off .
First guy to capture the flag wins , and that 's about it .
I still don 't understand why you got so upset about last night .
I wasn 't doing anything that bad , was I ?
I 'm sorry , Paul . I just wasn 't ready . I just ...
- Hey , I understand . - Please don 't .
What 's the matter with you ?
I have to go .
Angela !
- Angela ! - Let her go .
I really don 't know why you keep bothering with her .
She 's so small .
- What do you know ? - I know a lot of things .
Angela , you gotta help me . I got a great plan to get the flag .
We cut through the woods and sneak up behind them .
You go in one way and I go in the other .
It can 't miss !
- I don 't feel like playing , Ricky . - Oh , come on .
Help me out , will you ?
I can 't do it by myself .
Please ?
After we get the flag the game will be over and you won 't have to play anymore .
Okay ?
- Alright , where do we have to go ? - Follow me .
The flag should be around there , past those trees .
You go in from this side , and I 'll walk around
and attack from the other side .
They 'll never be able to catch both of us .
How do I know when to come out ?
Good question .
Tell you what .
Give me about five minutes , and when I see them run after you ,
I 'll sneak out and grab the flag .
- I hope it works . - No sweat , it 's foolproof .
Come on . No one will see us .
Jesus , will you loosen up already ?
That wasn 't so bad , was it ?
I guess not .
Angela !
Hey . Where are you going ?
You 're a real scumbag , Judy , you know that ?
Fuck you , Ricky .
You 're just jealous .
Same to you .
Mind if I sit here ?
Angela , I 'm really sorry about what happened before .
I really am .
I don 't know what happened . She just wouldn 't leave me alone .
Come on , Angela . Please ?
Give me another chance , will you ?
Please ?
Back together so soon ?
Boy , Angela , you sure are forgiving .
Especially after he told me what a prude you are .
That is the word you used ,
isn 't it , Paul ?
I gotta go .
Bye , Paul .
It 's really no big deal , you know .
I mean , he 's okay for you .
How about a little swim , huh , Angela ?
What do you say we get that beautiful bod of yours into the water , hmm ?
- Hello , Ricky . - Hi , Mel .
Seems we haven 't had much of a chance to talk .
How 's your summer been so far ?
- Alright , I guess . - Just alright ?
Well , it would have been better if there were more guys around .
It 's kind of hard to get a ball game up now , you know ?
Yeah .
It is a shame so many had to leave .
So how about it , Angela ? Let 's go for a swim .
Oh , what 's the matter ? You afraid ?
Huh ?
Well say something , you spoiled little bitch !
What 's the problem ?
My good friend Angela here
doesn 't feel like going in the water today .
Oh , she doesn 't , does she ?
Well , I think I can fix that .
No ! Stop it ! Let me down !
Stop it ! Please ! Don 't throw me in the water !
Please , let me go !
With all this bad publicity , I don 't see how I can hold onto the camp .
One sec ...
- I asked you a question ! - Hey , what are you doing ?
Just like all those other times . She gets into trouble and you run to her rescue .
You try to take care of everybody .
How you gonna do it this time ? Another drowning , or something worse ?
What are you talking about ? Let me go !
I saw you those times !
In the rec room , at the water fight , you killed them !
Stop it ! Don 't throw me in the water !
Stop , please ! I don 't know how to swim !
You killed them to destroy me , didn 't you ? Didn 't you ? !
Jesus Christ , Mel ! What the hell are you doing ?
Angela !
Oh , poor baby .
You 're a real peckerhead , you know that , Meg ?
Little fuckers !
Hey ! Animals ! Knock it off !
Calm down , Angela . It 's okay now .
Everything 's gonna be alright .
We won 't let them get away with this , that 's for sure .
I promise we won 't .
Okay , the only activity scheduled for tonight is a social in the rec room .
Those on duty can start bringing your kids up around nine ,
except for Eddie , who I 've got some bigger and better things planned .
- A night off ! - Even better than that .
Tonight you get to take those little darlings of yours
on a camping trip on the lake .
The campfire , sleeping under the stars , bacon and eggs for breakfast .
- I can 't wait . - Okay .
As for the rest of you , you 're all on tonight , except for ... Let me see ...
- Jerry and Meg . Any questions ? - Yea .
What 's that ?
Anybody want to switch ?
Sorry , Eddie . Have a good evening , everybody .
- Boy , are you lucky . - You ain 't kidding .
- I could sure use the night off . - You and the rest of us .
I 'll see you later , okay ?
Hey , guess who has the night off tonight ?
Well , congratulations .
Listen , I was thinking ... Remember that dinner you promised me ?
UP at your place ?
Yeah . Nine , nine-thirty ?
You got it . See you then .
What are you so happy about ?
- Got me a date tonight . - Oh yeah ? With who ?
It 's a secret .
I don 't suppose you guys would let me go next , would you ?
Didn 't think so .
Hey , Jude ! Jude ! Jude ! Is the water still on next door ?
- I guess so . - Great .
See you later .
Hey , no fighting back there .
Okay , guys , let 's go .
You guys got all that stuff out of the car , right ? Hey , quit it !
Give me that .
- This isn 't a toy ! - I wasn 't doing anything !
Look , guys , you set up and I 'll go get some wood for the fire , ok ?
Can I come , Eddie ?
What are you , my shadow ?
Alright . Alright . Come on , let 's go .
Hi .
Do you know where Ricky is ?
He 's back at the bunk lying down .
Said he didn 't feel good after dinner , but he might come by later .
Look , Angela .
I 'm really sorry about what I did . I know I was wrong .
Can 't you forgive me just this once ?
Please ?
I didn 't mean what I said about you .
I was just pissed off .
I swear it .
Excuse us , kids .
Don 't they make a lovely couple .
I really hate that girl .
Please , Angela . I 'm really sorry .
You know I am .
Please forgive me .
Please ?
Meet me at the waterfront after the social .
I 'll be there .
Eddie .
Eddie , I 'm cold .
- Eddie ! - What do you want ?
I want to go back . I 'm cold !
- Forget it . - Eddie !
- Please , Eddie , I want to go back . - I want to come too !
You guys are really pains in my ass , you know that ?
Please ?
Alright . Up to the car .
Susie ?
Have you seen Meg anywhere ?
- She 's off tonight , Mel . - Yeah , I know .
She was supposed to meet me about an hour ago .
Did you check the bunk ?
Not yet .
If you see her , tell her I 'm looking for her . Will you , please ?
- Do you have to kiss so wet ? - Sorry .
Quick . Under the bed .
- Hi , Mel . - Hey ,
You 're not going to the social tonight , eh ?
I 'm a little tired , so I thought I might get to bed early .
Oh , yeah ? I 'm looking for Meg , have you seen her ?
The last time I saw Meg , she was going next door to take a shower .
- When was that ? - I don 't know .
After dinner sometime .
Alright , thanks .
You know , you could ruin your eyes reading in the dark like that .
Look . I think I 'd better beat it .
What ?
You just got here !
I don 't know , I just don 't want to get caught .
Cut the crap , Mike . He won 't be back and you know it .
You never know . Look , I 'll see you tomorrow .
Don 't bet on it .
Chickenshit .
Meg ?
Are you in there ?
Oh my God .
Not you , Meg .
He did this to get back at me !
I had him . I had him and let him go .
Forgive me , Meg , please forgive me .
I 'll stop him .
I 've got to stop him !
He won 't get away , Meg .
He 'll never get away from me again .
Mike ?
Is that you ?
Who is that ?
Well , whoever it is , don 't turn the light on ,
or we 'll have to go to the stupid social .
Oh , it 's you . What do you want ?
Well ?
Help .
Somebody .
Help ! Help !
Somebody help !
Wait a minute . Where do you think you 're going ?
- Inside , to get something to eat . - Oh , no . The social 's over .
Get back to your bunk .
Give me a break , huh ?
I 've been lying down all night because dinner made me sick .
Just let me grab something real quick .
Well , dinner was shitty .
- Just make it snappy . - Thanks , Jeff .
Hello ?
Speaking .
What ?
Oh , God , no .
Three of them ?
Listen , I 'll get them now . Right now , I will .
I just don 't believe it , though .
I gotcha now , you little monster . Now it 's my turn !
Get the fuck off of me ! Leave me alone !
You killed that Benny and Billy just like you left Meg !
I don 't know what the fuck you 're talking about !
I didn 't do nothing !
Stop it ! I didn 't do anything , you crazy fuck !
Stop it ! I didn 't do nothing !
Liar ! Liar ! Liar !
Marie , find all the counselors and have them meet me in my shack right away .
I 'll go get the ones below .
- What happened ? - Just get them !
Liar !
I got him . Just like I promised Meg .
I got him .
Wait .
I gotta get away .
It can 't be you .
It can 't be !
- I filled them all in . - Alright , great .
Now I suggest you send them all back to their kids
to make sure everyone stays inside .
- Angela and Judy are missing . - Oh , no .
- What 's all the fuss ? - There 's a killer loose .
Make sure no one leaves your bunk for any reason .
Paul and Ricky haven 't come back yet .
We 'd better go look for them right now .
Everybody out in pairs .
Look everywhere you can think of , even the empty cabins .
Let me get my flashlight .
I didn 't think you were gonna show .
- Let 's go swimming . - Now ?
- What about our clothes ? - Take them off .
OK !
Found one .
Ricky .
Hey , he 's alive !
It 's Meg .
It 's so horrible !
Angela !
Judy !
Ricky , Paul ! You guys out here ?
Hey . You hear something ?
- What ? - Listen .
Sounds like singing .
Damn it . It 's coming from over here .
It 's Angela !
Angela ! Are you alright ?
Angela ! Are you okay ?
Angela , can you hear me ?
Oh , you 're going to enjoy living with us so much !
Yes , I know you are .
As a welcome-home present I bought you such wonderful new clothes .
I just hope that Richard doesn 't get jealous that I didn 't get him anything .
Oh , but then he is such a dear . I 'm sure that he won 't mind .
You see , I 've always wanted a little girl .
But of course , when my husband left ...
Oh , well !
That 's all water under the bridge , as I always say .
Water under the bridge .
But it certainly will be a nice little surprise when Richard comes home
to find a little girl in the house .
Yes , I 've always dreamed of a little girl just like you .
I mean , we already have a boy .
So another one simply would not do . Oh , no , absolutely not .
A little girl would be so much nicer . Don 't you think so , Angela ?
Angela ...
Such a lovely name .
Why , I believe it means " angel " .
Why , yes . I 'm sure it does .
I know you 're going to like that name .
Won 't you , Peter ?
How can it be ?
My God , she 's a boy .